Guide to the J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers, 1964-1968
Department of Special Collections
J. Arthur (Jesse Arthur) Younger Papers,
1964-1968
Special Collections M0216
Younger, J. Arthur, (Jesse Arthur), 1893-1967.
12 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
None.
Provenance
Gift of Representative Paul McCloskey, Jr., 1972.
Biographical Note
Jesse Arthur Younger, born 11 April 1893, Albany, Oregon, graduated from the University of Washington at Seattle, 1915, and served in World War I. He was the representative from the 9th California Congressional District to the United States House of Representatives, 1953-1967. He died 20 June 1967.
Scope and Content
Correspondence, documents, and printed reference materials which form a written record of Younger's career in Washington, D.C. from 1964 until his death in 1967 and the election of his successor. Covers almost every aspect of his life and duties as well as showing his constituents' reactions and opinions to most of the major and local issues of the period.
Arrangement Note
The files are arranged alphabetically by subject (Boxes 1 through 6) followed by Correspondence arranged alphabetically.
Container List
- Subject files
  - Administration - Public Opinion (90th Congress, 1967) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, General (90th Congress, 1967) (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Air Pollution (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alcatraz (90th Congress, 1967 - 1968),EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - American Legion (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annapolis, Annual Trip (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Appointments for Constituents (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Area Redevelopment (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Armed Services, General (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Army, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Army, Dept. of (Engineers), (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Army, Dept. of (Engineers), (89th Congress, 1966) (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Army, Dept. of (Engineers), (88th Congress, 1965) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Army, Dept. of (Meningitis), (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arnsten, Mr. and Mrs. E. B., (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Arts (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Assassination, President Kennedy (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Energy (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Aviation (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Awards, General (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Banking and Currency (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bankruptcy (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bills, Index (88th and 89th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bills (88th Congress, 1st Session) - HR 1566 - HR1573, HR 4872, HR 6631, HR 7026, HR 9093, HR 9422 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Bills (88th Congress, 2nd Session) - HR 10733, HR 11872, HR 11959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Birth Certificates (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Books (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Boy Scouts (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Budget (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Burials (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - California, Bay Fill and San Luis Drain (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - California, State of (General), (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - California, State of (General). (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - California, State of (Congressional Delegation) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - California, State of (Legislation) (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - California, State of (Reapportionment, 90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - California, State of (State Society, 90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Capitol (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Cemeteries (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Census (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Central Intelligence Agency (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Civil Aeronautics Board (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Civil Defense (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Civil Rights (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Civil Service (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Civil Service, William J. Stalzer (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Clubs (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Coast Guard (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Coast Guard Academy (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Colma Creek Flood Control Project (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Colma Creek Flood Control Project (89th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Commemorations (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Commerce, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Committees, General (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Committees, Interstate (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Committees, Joint on Organization of Congress (90th Congress) EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Committees, Rules (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Committees, Senate (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Committees, Statements Before (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Committees, Un-American Activities (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Communications (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Communism (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Compensation (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Congress (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Congressional Records, Correspondence (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Congressional Records, General (1967) (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Congressional Records Mailing List (1967) (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Connally Amendment (Reservation) (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Contracts (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Copyrights and Patents (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Courts (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Crimes and Offenses (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Customs (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Daly City Beach Erosion (90th Congress) (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Daly City Beach Erosion (88th Congress, 1963) (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Defense (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Disarmaments (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Disaster Areas (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - District of Columbia (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Donations (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Economy (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Education (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - El Granada Beach Erosion (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - El Granada Beach Erosion (88th Congress, 1963) (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - El Granada Beach Erosion (88th Congress, 1963) (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Employment (summer)(90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Employment-Unemployment (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Exports (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Fairs (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Federal Aviation Agency (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Federal Bureau of Investigation (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Federal Communications Commission (Sept., 1967) (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Federal Communications Commission (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Federal Power Commission (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Federal Trade Commission (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Flags, Bellamy Award (89th Congress, 1965 - 1966),EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Flags, General (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Fluoridation (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Flower Growers (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Food and Drug (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Football Tickets (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Foreign Affairs (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Foreign Affairs, Middle East (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Foreign Affairs, Rhodesia (taken to field office, 7/67) (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Foreign Affairs, Vietnam (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Foreign Affairs, Vietnam (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Foreign Trade (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Foundations and Funds (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Genealogy (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - General Accounting Office (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - General Service Administration (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Gifford, Mrs. Geraldine (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Government, General (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Government Printing Office (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Half Moon Bay Airport (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Half Moon Bay (Rebuilding Sewer Line) (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Harrison, Frank, EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Health and Welfare, General (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Highways (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Hospitals (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Housing, General (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Immigration (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Immigration and Naturalization Service (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Imports (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Inauguration ( 1969,90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Indian Affairs (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Insurance, General (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Interior, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Internal Revenue Service (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - International Affairs Seminars (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Interstate Commerce Committee (90th Congress) (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Introductions, Letters of (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Justice, Dept. of (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Juvenile Delinquency (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Labor, General (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Labor, Railroad Strikes (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Labor, Airline Strikes (90th Congress), EMPTY (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Legislation: Agriculture, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Legislation: Armed Services, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Legislation: Appropriations, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Legislation: Banking and Currency, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Legislation: District of Columbia, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Legislation: Education and Labor, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Legislation: Education and Labor, General (90th Congress beginning November, 1967) (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Legislation: Foreign Affairs, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Legislation: Government Operations, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Legislation: House Administration, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Legislation: Interstate and Foreign Commerce, General (1967) (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Legislation: Interstate and Foreign Commerce, Humane Treatment (1967) (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Legislation: Interstate and Foreign Commerce, May 1 -- (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Legislation: Interstate and Foreign Commerce, June 1 -- (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Legislation: Interstate and Foreign Commerce, September 1 -- (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Legislation: Interstate, hours of service (1967) (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Legislation: Interstate, Krebiozen (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Legislation: Interior and Insular, General (1967) (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Legislation: Interior and Insular, General (Sept., 1967) (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Legislation: Judiciary, General (1967) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Legislation: Judiciary, Burnham Chemical (88th Congress) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Legislation: Judiciary, Civil Rights (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Legislation: Judiciary, Firearms (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Legislation: Judiciary, Prayer Amendment (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Legislation: Merchant Marine and Fisheries (1967) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous, Ballots -- N. F. I. B. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Legislation: Miscellaneous, Ballots -- Opinion (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Legislation: Post Office and Civil Service, General (1967) (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Legislation: Public Works, General (1967) (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Legislation: Rules, General (1967) (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Legislation: Science and Astronautics (1967) (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Legislation: Small Business Committee, General (1967) -EMPTY (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Legislation: Un-American Activities (1967) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Legislation: Veterans' Affairs, General (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Legislation: Ways and Means, General (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Legislation: Medicare (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Legislation: Social Security (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Legislation: Taxes (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Ladera Dam (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Liaison Office (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Libraries, Congressional (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Libraries, Depository (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Libraries, General (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Lumber (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Mail Order Shipments (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Maritime Administration (90th Congress)- EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Millard, Steve (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Mining, General (90th Congress)- EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Missing Persons (90th Congress) EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Muse, Miss Fannie (90th Congress (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Narcotics (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - National Anthem (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - NASA (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - National Guard, General (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - National Parks and Forests (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Navy, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - New Citizens (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Newsletter, General (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Newspapers, General (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - News Releases (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - O'Hara, H. Richard (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Orphanages (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Pacifica, Beach Erosion (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Pages (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Pardons and Paroles (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Passports and Visas (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Peace Corps, General (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Pensions, General (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Pescadero Creek (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Pescadero Creek (89th Congress, 1965) (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Pescadero Creek (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Photographs (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Photography (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Pillar Point Breakwater (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Pillar Point Breakwater (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Political, General (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Political, Special Election - McCloskey (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Political, Special Election - McCloskey (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Political, Special Election, Oct. 1, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Political, Special Election, Oct. 23, 1967 - (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Political, Special Election, Nov. 8, 1967 - (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Population Explosion (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Pornography (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Post Office, General (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Post Office, Atherton (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Post Office, Belmont (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Post Office, Belmont (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Post Office, Brisbane (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Post Office, Brisbane (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Post Office, Burlingame (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Post Office, Burlingame (1963) (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Post Office, Daly City (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Post Office, Daly City (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Post Office, El Granada (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Post Office, Half Moon Bay (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Post Office, International Airport (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Post Office, International Airport (89th Congress, 1965) (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Post Office, La Honda (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Post Office, La Honda, (88th Congress, 1963) (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Post Office, Menlo Park (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Post Office, Menlo Park (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Post Office, Millbrae (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Post Office, Pacifica (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Post Office, Pacifica (1963) (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Post Office, Redwood City (90th Congress) (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Post Office, Redwood City (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - Post Office, San Bruno (90th Congress (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Post Office, San Bruno (88th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Post Office, San Carlos (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Post Office, San Mateo (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Post Office, San Mateo (89th Congress, 1965 - 1966) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Post Office, San Mateo (88th Congress, 1963) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Post Office, South San Francisco (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Presidents' Messages (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Presidential Succession (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Public Lands (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Public Utilities, General (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Public Utilities, Woodside, accelerator (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Publications, Agricultural Bulletins (1967) (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Publications, Agricultural Yearbooks (1967) (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Publications, Congressional Quarterly (1967) (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Publications, Debate Topics (1967) (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Publications, Distributed (1967) (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Publications, Family Fare (1967) (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Publications, Federal Register (1967) -EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Publications, Infant Care (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Publications, Received (Sept., 1967) (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Publications, Received (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Publications, Requested, June 1 -- (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Publications, Requested, April 1 - May 31, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Publications, Requested (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Publications, Requested by us (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Questionnaires, General (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Questionnaires, Fiesta (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Questionnaires, Younger (90th Congress, 1967) -EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Questionnaires, Younger (90th Congress, 1968) -EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Radio, TV and Movies (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Railroads (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Real Estate (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Recommendations (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Redwood City, Port of (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Redwood City, Port of (89th and 90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Redwood City, Port of (88th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Redwood City, Port of, Project (1961 - 1962) (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Referrals (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Religion, General (90th Congress (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Resolutions, General (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - San Carlos Airport (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - San Francisco International Airport (89th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - San Francisco International Airport (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - San Francisco Naval Shipyard (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - San Francisquito Creek (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - San Francisquito Creek (89th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - San Gregorio Creek (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - San Mateo, County of, General (May 1, 1967 -) (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - San Mateo, County of (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - San Mateo, Streams Flowing West (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Science and Space Program (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Security Checks (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Selective Service (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Senate, General (90th Congress) (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Sensenbrenner, Jim (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Shipping, General (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Small Business (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Social Security, Beginning 4/1/67(90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Social Security, Beginning 4/1/67(90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Socialism (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, Other than Younger (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Sports (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - State, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Steel (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Stockpile, General (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Supreme Court (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Surplus (90th Congress) - Property (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Tariffs (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Taxes, Income (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Taxes, General (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Transportation, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Travel, General (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Treasury, Dept. of (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Treaties (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Trucking (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - United Nations (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - United States Information Agency (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Uppman, Miss Ingegerd (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Veterans' Administration (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Visitors: Sept., 1967(90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Visitors: June, 1967(90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Visitors (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Voting, General (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Voting, Younger (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - War on Poverty (Beginning April 1, 1967,90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - War on Poverty, General (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Water Resources (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - West, Walter M. (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - West Point, Annual Trip (90th Congress) - EMPTY (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - White House (90th Congress) (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1966-1967
  - Correspondence: Aa - Gr (1966 - 1967) (Box 7)
  - Correspondence: Gr - O (1966 - 1967) (Box 8)
  - Correspondence: O - Z (1966 - 1967) (Box 9)
J. ARTHUR YOUNGER ADDITION NAME INDEX
Adair, E. Ross (1907 -) 1 6
Adams, Brock 5 54
Allen, Rober H. 1 12
Ashbrook, John M. 4 34
Ball, Robert M. (1914 -) 1 46 6 3
Battaglia, Philip M. 1 46
Bayh, Birch 3 4
Beek, Joseph A. 1 49
Belcher, Page (1899 -) 2 63
Bell, Alphonzo 1 46
Bennett, Charles E. (1910 -) 1 78
Bertucelli, Frank J. 1 66
Blackwell, J. L. 1 10
Boerger, Frank C. 1 11
Bow, Frank T. 1 83 3 3
Boyd, Alan S. 2 39
Britschgi, Carl A. 2 31
Brody, Ralph M 1 46
Brotzman, Donald G. 5 13
Brown, Edmund G. (1905 -) 5 36
Broyhill, Joel T. (1919 -) 1 78
Buckley, Charles A. (1890 -) 2 9
Cannon [UNK] (1879 -) 5 36
Celler, Emanuel (1888 -) 1 24 3 10
Chase, Russell 1 21
Clausen, Don H. 3 7
Cliff, Edward P. 1 2 1 11
Cohen, Kenneth 2 63
Cohen, Wilbur J. 1 40 2 41
Collier, John L. E. Bud 1 49
Collier, A. S., Jr. 1 9
Corbett, Robert J. (1905 -) 3 19
Cowger, William O. 2 26
Dillard, John A. B. 1 11
Dorsey, Stephen P. 1 24
Farrell, Raymond F. 2 48
Feighan,,ichael A. 1 28
Findley, Paul 2 70
Flournoy, J. D. 1 46
Goodell, Charles E. (1926 -) 6 33
Graham, Jackson 1 12
Gronouski, John A. 4 50
Gruening, Ernest (1887 -) 4 39
Guernsey, Edward J. 6 28
Hill, Lester 5 34
Holifield, Chet 1 48
Hoover, J. Edgar (1895 -) 2 15
Johnson, Harold T. 2 63
Kauffmann, Draper L. 1 6
Krebs, Ward G. 1 42
Langen, Odin 1 2
Lee, Robert E. (1912 -) 2 16
Lipscomb, Glenard P. (1915 -) 2 31
Loevinger, Lee 2 73
MacArthur, Douglas II (1909 -) 2 47 6 8
MackCarter, John 2 30
Marshall, Clyde M. 1 1
McCloskey, Paul N., Jr. 2 38 5 40
Mills, Wilbur D. (1909 -) 3 27
Moore, Tom 1 3
Murphy, George A. (1902 -) 5 35
Nes, Charles M., Jr. 1 52
O'Brien, Lawrence F. (1917 -) 4 40
Pendergast, J. Frank 2 40
Perkins, Carl D. (1912 -) 2 69
Pick, Lewis A., Jr. 1 11
Prescott, Robert W. (1913 -) 1 19
Preston, E. R. 1 12